hello everyone and welcome back to Coach
Twiggy youtube channel
it is raining outside honestly it's it's
kind of a deluge out there for those of
you that don't know what that means
means a whole lot of rain so I'm in my
garage today and we're bringing you a
quick little video here I typically
don't do a lot of product reviews but
for those of you that maybe don't know
my story or you're not familiar last
year I lost the vision in my right eye a
ball was hit through an L screen hit me
directly in the eyeball and it burst my
eyeball went through three pretty
gruesome surgeries and unfortunately
they were not able to save my vision so
I thought you know what I'm gonna be
shopping for my new L screen this might
be a good time for a product review so
that's what we're gonna do here today
the thing that we're gonna be reviewing
today is my new L screen and the first
thing you might notice as you look at it
is it's not in the shape of an L well
that's because this is a new net from
champ Rose Sports and it is called a Z
net you have an accident like that
obviously you shop around when it comes
to protecting your other eye as we know
we only have two and I've got to do
everything I can to protect my other eye
the champ pro sports Z net comes in two
different grades
there is a light grade which is a gray
frame and a little bit lighter net
probably made more for individual use
it's lighter frame lighter net therefore
it's obviously not as strong not as
heavy
I wanted the strongest Z screen that I
could get I also wanted the thicker of
the two nets as obviously that gives us
better protection I also like the fact
that it's heavy for when it's up in my
batting cage my batting cage is very
and I've had some cheaper l screens
previous to this and the one thing that
drives you crazy is when they're blowing
all around inside your cage and getting
stuck in the net so I wanted to get
myself a pretty heavy dude you want and
I think chat pro sports has definitely
delivered here the directions for this Z
screen were ridiculously simple all of
the pieces are numbered you basically
start with the lower numbers at the
bottom the feet are part 1 the middle
section is part 2 the sides
part 3 the Z section of the screen is
part 4 and the part that goes over the
top is part number 5 so basically if you
can count to 5 you can put this together
rather easily it's got the little push
pins that snap together and this
literally once it was out of the box and
I had the pieces out of the plastic and
the net out of the bag literally five
minutes it was up and it was ready the
net did come with some bungee cords that
you can put around the bottom I chose to
use very thick zip strips at the bottom
is that something I've grown accustomed
to using not that I don't like the
bungees but the bungees do really give
out kind of quickly and the weather due
to the Sun due to the rain due to the
cold due to the warmth and I find that
when is it strip breaks you simply
replace it and you're back in order what
makes the Z screen so unique and perfect
for me is that you can do baseball and
softball I work with a lot of baseball
players I work with a lot of softball
players so obviously when I'm throwing
BP to my baseball players I'm going to
be right here on this side and I'm going
to be thrown in here and then when I
turn the net around I can throw a
softball here so we've got both softball
and baseball and as you see it's really
easy to hide behind this there's no
framing going through the middle that's
blocking our vision I can see the hitter
very easily and I can do just about
with the net obviously I can probably
also set up on a bucket on this side and
I can toss here I can also set up a
bucket here and I can toss here so the
net is very usable for many different
situations and honestly I love it and I
cannot wait to try and finally the
bottom line what's the price
the lightweight model of this came in at
$99 free shipping the heavy-duty was one
$39.99 so basically one hundred and
forty dollars and I just thought for the
extra forty dollars you're getting a
much thicker net net you're getting a
much stronger frame and when it comes to
protection I've learned that you can
never be too cautious and that you
should always get the best of the best I
hope that you've enjoyed my product
review again the champer of sports heavy
duty or industrial Z net if you have any
questions please reach out if you like
this video please click like and also
subscribe as we're going to continue to
bring you the best of the best in
baseball videos product reviews skills
drills and more thanks again for tuning
in to coach twigs YouTube channel